JENAVIE PATRICK
3293 Charles. St Cottonwood, CA 96022 ● 925-812-3042
Jenavie.L.Patrick@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

I'm a hard-working, dedicated professional with 3 years medical office, billing and coding, 5 years management experience and 10 years Experience in Customer service. My experience includes client services/Reception working with Customers in the veterinary field and office setting. Medical billing and Customer service is one of my strong suits and I take pride in building strong, lasting working Relationships with Coworkers and Clients.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Dignity Health Medical Foundation *Cardiology dept.*

Redding, CA September 2019-current Medical office representative

- -Responsible for answering phones, sending and receiving referrals, and scheduling new and returning patients, triage appointments, worker compensation, and Veterans affairs appointments.
- Proficient in medical records with GECB and Cerner software including medical billing, and insurance verification.
- Responsibilities also include medical reception, such as checking patients in and out and collecting prepayment for clinic services.

# **Riverside Eyecare Professionals**

Redding, CA November 2017- September 2019 Medical account representative/ medical billing specialist

- Preparing encounter forms for a patients visit, posting insurance and patient payments.
- Basic knowledge of some ophthalmology terms, vocabulary, and conditions. Extensive knowledge of CMS 1500, UB04, ICD-9-CM, ICD-10 and CPT-4. Billing specialist outpatient and ambulatory surgery center claims
- -Responsible for answering phones, sending and receiving referrals, and scheduling new and returning patients, triage appointments, worker compensation, and Veterans affairs appointments.
- Proficient in medical records with Nextgen software including medical billing, and insurance verification.
- Responsibilities also include medical reception, such as checking patients in and out and collecting prepayment for surgeries and clinic services.

- Preparing surgery charts including verifying an abundance of different insurance plans for a surgery center and a clinic for professional and facility charges.
- Knowledge of all office machines and programs such as a fax, phones, excel, power point, word, scanning and uploading documents to a patients paper or electronic medical record or chart.

## **VCA Companion Animal Hospital**

Redding, CA July 2017-November 2017

Receptionist/ Client Service Coordinator

- Greeting Clients, patients and potential clients, being the first Of VCA
- Answer a Multiple Phone line, send faxes, emails, Data entry, and uploading scans.
- Admitting and discharging Patients including taking Financial transactions for Clients.
- Preparation and maintenance of Medical Records; including scanning and uploading paper charts and medical records to Woofware program, and sending appropriate records that have been requested to other hospitals or clients.
- Have an Understanding of All Vaccinations, Basic Lab test, common Diseases, and Pet behavior.
- Schedule, reschedule, Cancel and confirm all appointments and procedures, with Hospital's proper protocols.

# **VCA Cottage Animal Hospital**

Walnut creek, CA July 2016-July 2017

Receptionist/ Client Service Coordinator

- Greeting Clients, patients and potential clients, being the first friendly face Of VCA
- Answer a Multiple Phone line, send faxes, emails, Data entry, and uploading scans with urgency and care.
- Admitting and discharging Patients including taking Financial transactions for Clients. Also, rooming and preparing exam rooms for patients.
- Preparation and maintenance of Medical Records; including scanning and uploading paper charts and medical records to Woofware program, and sending appropriate records that have been requested to other hospitals or clients.
- Have an Understanding of All Vaccinations, Basic Lab test, common Diseases, and Pet behavior.
- Schedule, reschedule, Cancel and confirm all appointments and procedures, with Hospital's proper protocols.
- Create Treatment Plans For Clients to Initial for procedures; Prepare Health Certificates According to State Regulations and Hospital Protocol for Traveling Purposes.

### Ike's Love and Sandwiches

Danville. Ca

Store Manager, May, 2014 - July, 2016

- Manage a team of 15 employees
- Assisting the General Manager with preparing budgets, track expenses and provide monthly

financial reports by utilizing Microsoft Excel

- Processes clerical tasks as a liaison between the Accounting and Human Resources departments
- Manage daily deposits and banking records
- Oversees preparation of food, menus and beverages with full authority of inventory and ordering
- Certified by ServSafe as a Food Protection Manager through 2018 to assist in food production, catering orders, online orders, phone orders and cashiering

#### Treat's Café

Concord, Ca

General Manager, Dec., 2011- May, 2014

- Recruited, managed, trained and scheduled a team of 6 or more employees
- Responsible for timecard collection and accuracy to submit to 3rd party payroll vendors
- Maintained store budget, tracked expenses and provided monthly financial reports for the owner
- Ordered supplies, received and organized deliveries, on a weekly basis
- Acted as primary contact for customer orders, inquiries and/or complaints
- Ordered marketing materials and managed social networking sites

#### **Marie Callender's Restaurant**

Concord . Ca

Server / Cashier, June, 2009-Oct., 2011

- Maintained a high degree of customer service while taking orders and serving guests
- Answered multiple phone lines for pie and take-out orders
- Greeted and seated new and returning customers
- Cashiered and settled cash drawer

#### LeGateau Elegant

Martinez. Ca

Front Cashier, Pastry Baker / Decorator, Dec., 2008 – Jun, 2009

- Took cake orders and scheduling wedding cake tastings via multi-line phone system
- Provided exceptional customer service to all clientele
- Baked and decorated multiple cakes and pastries
- Prepared and served a variety of pastries and coffee beverages
- Organized Orders By priority to ensure deadlines were met
- Assisted with clerical duties, as needed
- Maintained cleanliness and organization of store and pastry cases

#### **EDUCATION**

Alhambra High School, Martinez, CA High School Diploma, 2009

# References

Amy Olsen DVM Doctor of Veterinary Medicine (650)346-2092

Pansy Suzuki DVM Doctor of Veterinary Medicine (626)205-4612

Rachel Bayliss General Manager Ike's love and sandwiches (925)826-8124